



416 - 559 - 7043



nicole.augello@ontariotechu.net



www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-augello



Bolton, ON

# **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor of Commerce Honours**

Ontario Tech University
Oshawa, ON

\*Presidents list academic achievement

#### **Secondary School**

St. Michaels Catholic Secondary School Bolton, ON

# **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Excel Proficient
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- QuickBooks
- SAP Certified
- Project Management
- Highly Organized
- Quick Learner
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

# Nicole Augello

Senior Mortgage Administrator / Real Estate Appraiser

### SUMMARY PROFILE

Graduate from Ontario Tech University with a Bachelor of Commerce Honours degree, with an area of study in accounting and international business practices.

Previously a varsity athlete, playing for our University women's hockey team. Attaining the ability to maximize team cohesion and take a leadership role among others.

My long-term goals include finding a career/position that challenges me, keeps me engaged, and allows me to contribute to the greater good of a team and organization.

My experiences in customer service and my forward-thinking mindset are what make me a great asset to any team. I am a passionate, enthusiastic, and positive person who seeks opportunities to further develop my skill-set.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Equitable Bank

Toronto, ON 2022 - Current

# Appraisal Advantage Canada

Toronto, ON 2021 - 2022

# **MAV Beauty Brands**

Vaughan, ON 2019 - 2020

# **Toronto Ponds** and Water Features

Toronto, ON 2018

# UOIT Ridgeback Hockey Camp

Oshawa, ON Summers

# Bolton Family Foot Care

Bolton, ON 2015 - 2017

# **Senior Administrator / Payments**

# Mortgage Service Admin / Payments

- Processing mortgage transactions
- Preparing statements/calculations.
- Actioning insurance notices (renewals and cancelations)
- Processing bill and wire payments
- Reconciling statements and reports

### **Residential Real Estate Appraiser**

- Organize/schedule, applicant appointments & lender phone calls.
- Manage 25-30 ongoing orders, and complete 3-5 appraisals daily.
- Analyze real estate market trends.
- Conduct physical inspections and analytical appraisal analysis.
- Professionally communicate with applicants/homeowners/lenders.

### **Accounting Intern / Data Analytics**

- Accounts Payable, Accounts Receivable, and Data Analytics'
- Inputting invoices, sending cheques and wire transfers
- Reconciling vendor debts to master budget, forecasting future values.
- Analyzing retailer's sales values, pivoting the information, creating models for sales and marketing.

# **General Labour / Schedule Organizer**

- Organizing daily schedule via excel.
- Fix, build, and clean home water features such as waterfalls/ponds
- Kindly greet clients, complete current job and promote other services we offer.

#### **Athletic Instructor for Kids**

- Full daycare of children ages 8-12.
- On-ice instructor, run fun, active, and educational drills for kids.
- Off-ice activity instructor. Health and wellness education and development.

# **Back Coordinator and Reception**

- Greeting patients, gathering information, and escorting.
- Sterilization of tools, in charge of stock and supply orders.
- Recording insurance information, discussing coverage and providing assurance companies with the analysis of treatments.